bodycentral.com 2014-06-26

# Privacy Policy | Body Central

BODY CENTRAL ONLINE PRIVACY POLICY  
Last modified: May 2014

1.    INTRODUCTION

    Purpose.  The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to describe how Body Central Direct (“Body Central”) collects, uses and shares information about you through our U.S. online interfaces (e.g., websites and mobile applications) owned and controlled by us, including www.bodycentral.com  (collectively referred to herein as the “Site”).  Please read this notice carefully to understand what we do. If you do not understand any aspects of our Privacy Policy, please feel free to 

[Contact Us](http://www.bodycentral.com/service/contact.aspx) or as described at the end of this Policy. 

    Our Privacy Policy explains: 

  *     Information  We Collect and Why We Collect It
  *     How We Use and Share Your Information
  *     Access to Your Information and Choices
  *     Security of Your Information
  *     California Privacy Rights
  *     International Privacy Practices
  *     Changes to Our Privacy Policy
  *     Questions and How Contact Us

    Scope; Third Party Sites.  This Privacy Policy applies only to information we collect at and through the Site, and certain Body Central affiliated sites accessible through our Site, such as investor.bodyc.com. Our Site also contains links to third party sites, including social media sites such as Facebook, Twitter and Pintrest, that are not owned or controlled by Body Central.  Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites.  We encourage you to be aware when you leave our Site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personal information.  

    Terms of Use.  Please note that your use of our Site is also subject to our 

[Terms of Use](http://www.bodycentral.com/service/terms.aspx).

2.    INFORMATION WE COLLECT AND WHY WE COLLECT IT

    Information You Provide To Us.  You can provide information to us on our Site through various means, including 

  * When you register at the Site and/or create an online account
  * On your account information page
  * When you purchase products from us
  * Contact us pages and forms
  * Newsletter sign-up
  * Favorites / wish lists
  * Online email forms
  * Information provided through your smart phone or mobile device
  * Feedback forms
  * Request for information forms
  * Sweepstakes, surveys, promotions or contests
  * When you provide user generated content such as user comments, blog posts and other social media communications

    The information we collect includes personal information, such as 

  * Name
  * Address
  * Billing address
  * Shipping address
  * Email address
  * Telephone number
  * Credit card number (solely for payment purposes)

No Information From Children Under Age 13.  If you are under the age of 13, please do not attempt to register with us at this Site or provide any personal information about yourself to us.  If we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under the age of 13, we will promptly delete that information.  If you believe we might have any information from a child under the age of 13, please [Contact U](http://www.bodycentral.com/service/contact.aspx)s or call Customer Service at (800) 741-9696. 

    Information We Collect Automatically.  We collect certain information automatically as you use our Site, such as 

  * IP address
  * Browser type
  * Computer or device type
  * Operating system version
  * The website from where you navigated to our Site
  * Time and date of using our Site
  * The pages on our Site that you view
  * The name of your Internet service provider (ISP)
  * Location / Geolocation information
  * Cookies  
  * Local shared objects (flash cookies)

Cookies.  When you visit our Site we send one or more “cookies” to your computer or other device. A cookie is a small file containing a string of characters that is sent to your computer when you visit a website. When you visit the website again, the cookie allows that site to recognize your browser. Cookies may store unique anonymous identifiers, user preferences and other information. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some website features or services may not function properly without cookies. We use cookies to improve the quality of our service, including for storing user preferences, tracking user trends and providing relevant advertising to you. See “Advertising and Marketing” below for additional information about cookies and advertising. 

    Pixel Tags.  We may use “pixel tags,” also known as “web beacons,” which are small graphic files that allow us to monitor the use of our websites.  A pixel tag is a type of technology placed on a website or within the body of an email for the purpose of tracking activity on websites, or when emails are opened or accessed, and is often used in combination with cookies. A pixel tag can collect information such as the IP (Internet Protocol) address of the computer that downloaded the page on which the tag appears; the URL of the page on which the pixel tag appears; the time the page containing the pixel tag was viewed; the type of browser that fetched the pixel tag; and the identification number of any cookie on the computer previously placed by that server. 

Text/SMS Messaging.  Body Central Alerts offers mobile access to various promotions and other announcements over SMS. Enrollment can be achieved by texting BODY to 62088 and following the double opt-in instructions provided to you over SMS. The mobile phone number's verification message along with all other SMS messages may have standard text and data rates that apply. Users will be allowed to opt-out of this program at any time by sending the message STOP to 62088 or by emailing [help@pgminf.com](mailto:help@pgminf.com) with the subject line “STOP” along with your 10 digit mobile number. Message frequency is no more than 10 autodialed SMS messages per month, however we will respond to each of your requests for information. Consent is not required to purchase goods or services from Body Central. 

If your mobile telephone number and/or mobile provider change, you agree to notify Body Central and provide your updated mobile telephone number and/or updated mobile provider. If you are sending an inbound text message to Body Central and do not receive a response, please contact your mobile provider for support. Some devices and mobile providers may not be SMS compatible, please contact your mobile provider for additional support.

You can contact us at 877-471-4885 with questions about the text messaging program, or by texting HELP to 62088.  
3.    HOW WE USE AND SHARE YOUR INFORMATION

    To Provide Products, Services, and Information.  As described above, we collect information from you so that we can provide products and services that you purchase using the Site, and provide information that you request from us.  We use your personal information to contact you about your orders, process credit card / debit card transactions, and ship products to you.  We may send you information about our products and services, and new offerings. We may provide information to third party service providers that help us process orders, and fulfill and deliver products and services that you purchase from us.

    We may use third parties to help host our Site, send out email updates about the Site, provide marketing and advertising services for us, remove repetitive information from our user lists, and process payments. These service providers will have access to your personal information in order to provide these services, but when this occurs we implement reasonable contractual and technical protections to limit their use of that information to helping us provide the service. We use demographic information to better understand our customers, and improve our products and services.

   Advertising and Marketing. We may use how you browse and shop in order to show you ads for Body Central or our advertising partners that are more relevant to your interests. We may use our own cookies and other information to provide relevant interest-based advertising to you. Interest-based ads are ads presented to you based on your browsing behavior in order to provide you with ads more tailored to your interests. These interest-based ads may be presented to you while you are browsing our site or third-party sites not owned by Body Central. You can opt-out of tracking for interest-based ads provided directly by Body Central by clicking [here](http://dtmc.bodycentral.com/adinfo/adchoices_fpc.html?cid=2507&cname=Body%20Central&cmagic=836917&clogo=bodycentral.png).

To learn more about the use of this information or choose not to have this information used by our third-party advertising partner by opting out please visit the Network Advertising Initiative by clicking [here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/). 

   For example, we use Criteo to provide online interest-based advertisements on our behalf. Criteo may place anonymous cookies on the browsers of visitors to our Site and may send their own cookies to the visitors’ cookie file. These cookies allow Criteo to display advertisements to visitors. Each advertisement provided by Criteo will include a link to Criteo’s Privacy Policy page that will include information for users on how to opt-out of being re/targeted. For more information about Criteo or to opt-out of receiving interest-based advertising from Criteo, please visit Criteo’s privacy policy at <http://www.criteo.com/us/privacy-policy>.

    We also use Dotomi to assist us with providing interest-based advertisements. For more information about Dotomi or to opt-out   
of receiving interest-based advertising from Dotomi, please visit Dotomi’s privacy policy at [http://www.dotomi.com/privacy/](http://www.dotomi.com/privacy). 

    Some third party websites may belong to ad networks that use your browsing history across websites to choose which ads to display on their sites; the displayed ads may include advertising for Body Central. To learn more, and to opt out of seeing interest-based advertisements on these sites, visit the Network Advertising Initiative and the Digital Advertising Alliance websites ([www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/) and [www.aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/)). Websites may also offer their own opt-out methods for interest-based advertising.

    Your Consent.  In addition to the sharing described elsewhere in this Policy, we will share personal information with companies, organizations or individuals outside of the Body Central when we have your consent to do so. We require opt-in consent for the sharing of any sensitive personal information. Sensitive personal information is a particular category of personal information relating to confidential medical facts, racial or ethnic origins, political or religious beliefs or sexuality. 

    Legal Proceedings.  We will share personal information with third party companies, organizations or individuals outside of Body Central if we have a good-faith belief that access, use, preservation or disclosure of the information is reasonably necessary to: 

  * Meet any applicable law, regulation, subpoena, legal process or enforceable governmental request.
  * Enforce applicable Terms of Use, including investigation of potential violations.
  * Detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues.
  * Protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of Body Central, our users, customers or the public as required or permitted by law.

    Transfer in the Event of Sale or Change of Control.  If the ownership of all or substantially all of our business changes or we otherwise transfer assets relating to our business or the Site to a third party, such as by merger, acquisition, bankruptcy proceeding or otherwise, we may transfer or sell your personal information to the new owner. In such a case, unless permitted otherwise by applicable law, your information would remain subject to the promises made in the applicable privacy policy unless you agree differently. 

4.    ACCESS TO YOUR INFORMATION AND CHOICES

    You can access and update certain information we have relating to your online account by logging into your account.  If you have questions about personal information we have about you or need to update your information, you can 

[Contact Us](http://www.bodycentral.com/service/contact.aspx) or call Customer Service at (800) 741-9696. You can opt-out of receiving marketing and promotional e-mails from Body Central by the following:  

  * Call Customer Service at (800) 741-9696 Monday-Friday 7AM-7PM EST and Saturday 9AM-1PM EST
  * Email Customer Service at customerservice@bodyc.com
  * Use the unsubscribe link contained in our marketing e-mails
  * Use the Catalog [Opt-out Link](http://www.bodycentral.com/service/catalog.aspx) in the [Contact Us](http://www.bodycentral.com/service/contact.aspx) section of our Site.

5.    SECURITY OF YOUR INFORMATION

    We use industry standard physical, technical and administrative security measures and safeguards to protect the confidentiality and security of your personal information.  However, since the Internet is not a 100% secure environment, we cannot guarantee, ensure, or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us.  There is no guarantee that information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of any of our physical, technical, or managerial safeguards.  It is your responsibility to protect the security of your login information.  Please note that e-mails and other communications you send to us through our Site are not encrypted, and we strongly advise you not to communicate any confidential information through these means. 

6.    INTERNATIONAL PRIVACY PRACTICES 

    Body Central’s websites, including websites directed to residents in countries and jurisdictions outside of the United States, are operated and managed on servers located and operated within the United States. By using and accessing our Sites, residents and citizens of countries and jurisdictions outside of the United States agree and consent to the transfer to and processing of personal information on servers located in the United States, and that the protection of such information may be different than required under the laws of your residence or location.

7.    CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY

    Our Privacy Policy may change from time to time. We will not reduce your rights under this Privacy Policy without your consent in accordance with applicable law. We will post any privacy policy changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice (including, for certain services, email notification of privacy policy changes). We will also keep prior versions of this Privacy Policy in an archive for your review. 

8.    QUESTIONS AND HOW CONTACT US

    If you have any questions, concerns, complaints or suggestions regarding our Privacy Policy or otherwise need to contact us, you can contact us by the following: 

  1. Use the [Contact Us](http://www.bodycentral.com/service/contact.aspx) link on the Site or email Customer Service at [customerservice@bodyc.com](mailto:customerservice@bodyc.com)
  2. Call Customer Service at Monday-Friday 7AM-7PM EST and Saturday 9AM-1PM EST
  3. Contact us through US postal mail at

Catalog/Website Inquiries

Attn: Customer ServiceBody Central  
6225 Powers Avenue  
Jacksonville, FL 32217
